good afternoon honourable members
the house is in committee
honourable members we are in committee
on the insurance prudential supervision
amendment bill and the question before
the house before the committee is it
part one stand part it's debate on
clauses three through to 17.
i call the honourable
david parker mr chairman thank you for
the call i have one question for the
minister and that is to
ascertain whether in uh agreeing
when when assessing whether these
regulations were necessary whether
consideration was given to the trade-off
between
greater
satisfaction with prudential margins and
the cost of insurance
that was an issue that i raised in an
earlier contribution and i haven't yet
had a reply from the minister
let's have a reply from the minister
all right
the question is that part one standpoint
all those in favor please say aye
the country no the eyes have it the
question now is at part two debated on
clauses 18 to 20 stand apart
oh i thought you were standing jerry
all right the question is that part two
stand part all those in favor please say
aye